

SDAVIS@KIHFICHARTFR.ORG

SODAVISTO@GMAIL.COM

808-214-2893

SOPHIAISFABULOUS.COM

ACADEMIC & PERSONAL OBJECTIVES

I would like to major in Biomedical Engineering in college and obtain a Ph.D. I would also like to attend medical school and specialize in pathology. I hope to achieve this through an MD Ph.D program at a research university. After grad school, I want to combine my interests in engineering and medicine to create a biomedical technologies startup. After having a startup and other engineering experience, I would like to become a professor at a research university.

WORK EXPERIENCE

SUMMER INTERN @

GOODFELLOW BROS., INC.

June 2017 - July 2017

Participated in the Women In Technology Stemworks Summer Internship and was assigned to Goodfellow Brothers, Inc. Learned about civil engineering and surveying. Worked on 3D models & surveying for sites around Maui County.

STUDENT HELPER I @ KIHEI PUBLIC LIBRARY

March 2016 - March 2017

Worked at Kihei Public Library for a year as a stuent helper. Duties included arranging, shelving, stamping, and labeling books. Also helped set up the kids crafts and did various assignments throughout the library.

INTERN @ NALUKAI FOUNDATION

June 2016 - July 2016

Worked with the Programming team for the new Nalukai website. Wrote some of the code (HTML, CSS) and inserted comments to help explain the code to future Nalukai campers.

SUMMER INTERN @ MAUI

June 2015 - July 2015

Participated in the Women In Technology Stemworks Summer Internship and was assigned to Maui Innovation Group. Worked on the electronics and android app for Maui Innovation Group's coconut harvesting robot.

EDUCATION

KIHEI CHARTER HIGH SCHOOL 2014 - 2018 GPA: 4.2 (usually but not currently) UNIVERSITY OF HAWAII MAUI COLLEGE 2015 - 2018 GPA: 3.51

SKILLS

PROGRAMMING

Proficient in HTML, CSS, Javascript, and C. Fairly experienced in Java, C++, and Python. Good at using the command line in UNIX based operating systems. Can pick up new languages quickly.

GENERAL STEM

Proficient at 3D modeling using Autodesk Inventor, Fusion 360, Sketchup.
Experienced with Civil 3d and Blender. Some graphic design experience.

ENGINEERING

Proficient at wiring, soldering, and building + designing circuits. Very experienced with Arduino and Raspberry Pi. Able to use oscilloscopes, multimeters, power supplies, and other electronics equipment

REFERENCES

LORRAINE PERRY

Library Technician at Kihei Public Library. Phone: (808) 875-6833

DARIUS 'BUBS' MONSEF

Founder of Nalukai Academy Hacker Camp Email: bubs@monsef.com

KEVIN CLARKE

Engineering Services at
Goodfellow Bros., Inc.
Email: kevinc@aoodfellowbros.com